Today we're going to be learning how to play Portal, a game by Valve Software.
A company with which I have no affiliation.
All right!
Here we are in test chamber 08.
We've got some new icons here now.
We've got the old familiar power ball death, power ball power conduit, and now it looks like we've got some other ones.
The risk of drowning and don't drink the water.
So we look here in test chamber 08.
We can see that the floor is actually sort of toxic goo.
The sort of toxic goo that you wouldn't want to find yourself in.
So we want to avoid hitting the floor of test chamber 08 at all costs.
We look over here on our left, we've got a power ball dispenser and an orange portal and a power conduit.
What we need to do is find a way to get the power ball over to the conduit and that will activate this elevator and let us get to the exit.
But we need to be careful because, if we come out of this orange portal and get hit by the power ball, we will die.
So we need to find a different way of doing things.